<mvc:View controllerName="sap.ui.Odata.webapp.controller.Faq"
		  xmlns:mvc="sap.ui.core.mvc" xmlns="sap.m"
		  class="whiteBackground"
>
	<Page showHeader="false" backgroundDesign="Solid">
		<mvc:XMLView viewName="sap.ui.Odata.webapp.view.Toolbar" />
		<content><IconTabBar selectedKey="cc" id="bar" backgroundDesign="Solid" headerBackgroundDesign="Solid" select="onSelect">
	            <items>
	                <IconTabSeparator/>
	                <IconTabFilter text="Cryptcurrency" icon="sap-icon://payment-approval" id="cryptcurrency" key="cc">
	                <content>
	                    <FeedListItem icon="sap-icon://personnel-view" text="What is cryptocurrency?" />
	                    <FeedListItem text="One of the most important problems that any payment network has to solve is double-spending. It is a fraudulent technique of spending the same amount twice. The traditional solution was a trusted third party - a central server - that kept records of the balances and transactions. However, this method always entailed an authority basically in control of your funds and with all your personal details on hand.&#10;&#10;In a decentralized network like Bitcoin, every single participant needs to do this job. This is done via the Blockchain - a public ledger of all transaction that ever happened within the network, available to everyone. Therefore, everyone in the network can see every account’s balance.&#10;&#10;Every transaction is a file that consists of the sender’s and recipient’s public keys (wallet addresses) and the amount of coins transferred. The transaction also needs to be signed off by the sender with their private key. All of this is just basic cryptography. Eventually, the transaction is broadcasted in the network, but it needs to be confirmed first." iconActive="false" selected="true" senderActive="false" showIcon="false" highlight="Information"/>
	                    <FeedListItem  icon="sap-icon://personnel-view" text="What is blockchain?" />
	                    <FeedListItem  text="A blockchain is a continuously growing list of records, called blocks, which are linked and secured using cryptography. Each block typically contains a cryptographic hash of the previous block, a timestamp and transaction data. By design, a blockchain is inherently resistant to modification of the data. It is &quot;an open, distributed ledger that can record transactions between two parties efficiently and in a verifiable and permanent way&quot;. For use as a distributed ledger, a blockchain is typically managed by a peer-to-peer network collectively adhering to a protocol for inter-node communication and validating new blocks. Once recorded, the data in any given block cannot be altered retroactively without the alteration of all subsequent blocks, which requires collusion of the network majority." iconActive="false" selected="true" senderActive="false" showIcon="false" highlight="Information"/>
	                    <FeedListItem  icon="sap-icon://personnel-view" text="Decentralization??" />
	                    <FeedListItem  text="By storing data across its peer-to-peer network, the blockchain eliminates a number of risks that come with data being held centrally. The decentralized blockchain may use ad-hoc message passing and distributed networking.&#10;&#10;Peer-to-peer blockchain networks lack centralized points of vulnerability that computer crackers can exploit; likewise, it has no central point of failure. Blockchain security methods include the use of public-key cryptography. A public key (a long, random-looking string of numbers) is an address on the blockchain. Value tokens sent across the network are recorded as belonging to that address. A private key is like a password that gives its owner access to their digital assets or the means to otherwise interact with the various capabilities that blockchains now support. Data stored on the blockchain is generally considered incorruptible.&#10;&#10;While centralized data is more easily controlled, information and data manipulation are possible. By decentralizing data on an accessible ledger, public blockchains make block-level data transparent to everyone involved.&#10;&#10;Every node in a decentralized system has a copy of the blockchain. Data quality is maintained by massive database replication and computational trust. No centralized &quot;official&quot; copy exists and no user is &quot;trusted&quot; more than any other.Transactions are broadcast to the network using software. Messages are delivered on a best-effort basis. Mining nodes validate transactions, add them to the block they are building, and then broadcast the completed block to other nodes. Blockchains use various time-stamping schemes, such as proof-of-work, to serialize changes. Alternate consensus methods include proof-of-stake.Growth of a decentralized blockchain is accompanied by the risk of node centralization because the computer resources required to process larger amounts of data become more expensive." iconActive="false" selected="true" senderActive="false" showIcon="false" highlight="Information"/>
	                </content>
	                </IconTabFilter>
	                <IconTabSeparator />
	                <IconTabFilter text="Bitcoin" icon="sap-icon://lead" id="bitcoin" key="btc">
	                    <content><FeedListItem xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:mvc="sap.ui.core.mvc" xmlns="sap.m" icon="sap-icon://personnel-view" text="What is bitcoin? How it appered?"/>
	                        <FeedListItem  text="Bitcoin is a cryptocurrency and worldwide payment system. It is the first decentralized digital currency, as the system works without a central bank or single administrator. The network is peer-to-peer and transactions take place between users directly, without an intermediary. These transactions are verified by network nodes through the use of cryptography and recorded in a public distributed ledger called a blockchain. Bitcoin was invented by an unknown person or group of people under the name Satoshi Nakamoto and released as open-source software in 2009.&#10;&#10;Bitcoins are created as a reward for a process known as mining. They can be exchanged for other currencies, products, and services. As of February 2015, over 100,000 merchants and vendors accepted bitcoin as payment. Research produced by the University of Cambridge estimates that in 2017, there were 2.9 to 5.8 million unique users using a cryptocurrency wallet, most of them using bitcoin." iconActive="false" selected="true" senderActive="false" showIcon="false" highlight="Information"/>
	                        <FeedListItem  icon="sap-icon://personnel-view" text="How it 's stored?"/>
	                        <FeedListItem  text="A wallet stores the information necessary to transact bitcoins. While wallets are often described as a place to hold or store bitcoins, due to the nature of the system, bitcoins are inseparable from the blockchain transaction ledger. A better way to describe a wallet is something that &quot;stores the digital credentials for your bitcoin holdings&quot; and allows one to access (and spend) them. Bitcoin uses public-key cryptography, in which two cryptographic keys, one public and one private, are generated. At its most basic, a wallet is a collection of these keys." iconActive="false" selected="true" senderActive="false" showIcon="false" highlight="Information"/>
	                    </content>
	                </IconTabFilter>
	                <IconTabSeparator />
	                <IconTabFilter  text="Mining" icon="sap-icon://home-share" iconColor="Positive" id="mining" key="min">
	                    <content>
	                        <FeedListItem  icon="sap-icon://personnel-view" text="How to obtain cryptocurrency?"/>
	                        <FeedListItem  text="In cryptocurrency networks, mining is a validation of transactions. For this effort, successful miners obtain new cryptocurrency as a reward. The reward decreases transaction fees by creating a complementary incentive to contribute to the processing power of the network. The rate of generating hashes, which validate any transaction, has been increased by the use of specialized machines such as FPGAs and ASICs running complex hashing algorithms like SHA-256 and Scrypt. This arms race for cheaper-yet-efficient machines has been on since the day the first cryptocurrency, bitcoin, was introduced in 2009. With more people venturing into the world of virtual currency, generating hashes for this validation has become far more complex over the years, with miners having to invest large sums of money on employing multiple high performance ASICs. Thus the value of the currency obtained for finding a hash often does not justify the amount of money spent on setting up the machines, the cooling facilities to overcome the enormous amount of heat they produce, and the electricity required to run them." iconActive="false" selected="true" senderActive="false" showIcon="false" highlight="Information"/>
	                        <FeedListItem  icon="sap-icon://personnel-view" text="Mining?"/>
	                        <FeedListItem  text="Mining is a record-keeping service done through the use of computer processing power. Miners keep the blockchain consistent, complete, and unalterable by repeatedly grouping newly broadcast transactions into a block, which is then broadcast to the network and verified by recipient nodes. Each block contains a SHA-256 cryptographic hash of the previous block, thus linking it to the previous block and giving the blockchain its name." iconActive="false" selected="true" senderActive="false" showIcon="false" highlight="Information"/>
	                        <FeedListItem  icon="sap-icon://personnel-view" text="What is a block?" />
	                        <FeedListItem  text="Blocks hold batches of valid transactions that are hashed and encoded into a Merkle tree. Each block includes the cryptographic hash of the prior block in the blockchain, linking the two. The linked blocks form a chain. This iterative process confirms the integrity of the previous block, all the way back to the original genesis block.&#10;&#10;Sometimes separate blocks can be produced concurrently, creating a temporary fork. In addition to a secure hash-based history, any blockchain has a specified algorithm for scoring different versions of the history so that one with a higher value can be selected over others. Blocks not selected for inclusion in the chain are called orphan blocks. Peers supporting the database have different versions of the history from time to time. They keep only the highest-scoring version of the database known to them. Whenever a peer receives a higher-scoring version (usually the old version with a single new block added) they extend or overwrite their own database and retransmit the improvement to their peers. There is never an absolute guarantee that any particular entry will remain in the best version of the history forever. Because blockchains are typically built to add the score of new blocks onto old blocks and because there are incentives to work only on extending with new blocks rather than overwriting old blocks, the probability of an entry becoming superseded goes down exponentially as more blocks are built on top of it, eventually becoming very low. For example, in a blockchain using the proof-of-work system, the chain with the most cumulative proof-of-work is always considered the valid one by the network. There are a number of methods that can be used to demonstrate a sufficient level of computation. Within a blockchain the computation is carried out redundantly rather than in the traditional segregated and parallel manner."  iconActive="false" selected="true" senderActive="false" showIcon="false" highlight="Information"/>
	                    </content>
	                </IconTabFilter>
	                <IconTabSeparator/></items>
	        </IconTabBar>
	    </content>
	</Page>

</mvc:View>